Finding aid for Department of Afroamerican and African Studies (University of Michigan) records, 1966-2010 (bulk 1970-1994)
Bentley Historical Library
- Audio recordings on cassettes, 1975-2001
  - Jamaica Study Abroad
    - Carolyn Cooper and Trevor Monroe: Cooper: Dynamics of Cultural Production (side a); 1991-06-17 - Monroe: Jamaican Political Economy; The Present Conjecture (side b), 1991 June 14; audiocassette; (Jamaican Political Economy: The Present Conjecture. Monroe, Trevor. Ann Arbor, Michigan. June 17, 1991. 1.5 of 1.5 Audio Cassette. 2.5 X 4 (Center for Afroamerican and African Studies. Jamaican Study Abroad); CAAS AV AC SA JAM 19.) (Box 29)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-95-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-95-2]
    - Trevor Monroe: Jamaican Political Economy: The Present Conjecture, 1991 June 17; audiocassette; (Jamaican Political Economy: The Present Conjecture. Monroe, Trevor. Ann Arbor, Michigan. June 17, 1991. 1.5 of 1.5 Audio Cassette. 2.5 X 4 (Center for Afroamerican and African Studies. Jamaican Study Abroad); CAAS AV AC SA JAM 20.) (Box 29)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-96-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-96-2]
    - Arnold Bertram and Joan Gordon-Wembley: Disaffected Perspectives on Jamaican Politics, 1991 June 18; audiocassette; (Disaffected Perspectives on Jamaican Politics. Bertram, Arnold and Gordon-Wembley, Joan. Ann Arbor, Michigan. June 18, 1991. 1.5 of 1.5 Audio Cassette. 2.5 X 4 (Center for Afroamerican and African Studies. Jamaican Study Abroad); CAAS AV AC SA JAM 21) (Box 29)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-97-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-97-2]
    - Arnold Bertram, Joan Gordon-Wembley and Rupert Lewis: Bertram & Gordon-Wembley: Disaffected Perspectives on Jamaican Politics" (side a); 1991-06-19 Lewis: Garvey Movement (side b), 1991 June 18; audiocassette; (Disaffected Perspectives on Jamaican Politics. Bertram, Arnold and Gordon-Wembley, Joan. Ann Arbor, Michigan. June 18, 1991. 1.5 of 1.5 Audio Cassette. 2.5 X 4 (Center for Afroamerican and African Studies. Jamaican Study Abroad); CAAS AV AC SA JAM 22.) (Box 29)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-98-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-98-2]
    - Rupert Lewis: Garvey Movement, 1991 June 19; audiocassette; (Garvey Movement. Lewis, Rupert. Ann Arbor, Michigan. June 19 1991. 1.5 of 1.5 Audio Cassette. 2.5 X 4 (Center for Afroamerican and African Studies. Jamaican Study Abroad).; CAAS AV AC SA JAM 23.) (Box 29)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-99-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-99-2]
    - Thomas Holt: The Problem of Freedom, 1991 June 19; audiocassette; (The Problem of Freedom. Holt, Thomas. Ann Arbor, Michigan. June 19, 1991. 1 Audio Cassette. 2.5 X 4 (Center for Afroamerican and African Studies. Jamaican Study Abroad); CAAS AV AC SA JAM 24.) (Box 29)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-100-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-100-2]
    - Velma Pollard: Reading Velma Pollard, 1991 June 20; audiocassette; (Reading Velma Pollard. Pollard, Velma Ann Arbor, Michigan. June 20, 1991. 1 Audio Cassette. 2.5 X 4 (Center for Afroamerican and African Studies. Jamaican Study Abroad); CAAS AV AC SA JAM 25.) (Box 29)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-101-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-101-2]
    - Irena Cousins, Donovan Crawford, Neville James and Paul Thomas: Panel Discussion on the Jamaican Business Environment, 1991 June 21; audiocassette; (Panel Discussion on the Jamaican Business Environment.Cousins, Irena; Crawford, Donovan; James, Neville; Thomas, Paul. Ann Arbor, Michigan. June 21, 1991. 1 Audio Cassette. 2.5 X 4 (Center for Afroamerican and African Studies. Jamaican Study Abroad); CAAS AV AC SA JAM 26.) (Box 29)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-102-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-102-2]
    - Irena Cousins, Donovan Crawford, Neville James, Paul Thomas and Elsa Leo-Rhynie: Cousins, et al: Panel Discussion on the Jamaican Business Environment (side a); 1991-06-24 - Leo-Rhynie: Status of Women in Jamaica (side b), 1991 June 21; audiocassette; (Panel Discussion on the Jamaican Business Environment. (1.5 of 1.5) Cousins, Irena; Crawford, Donovan; James, Neville; Thomas, Paul. Ann Arbor, Michigan. June 21, 1991. 1.5 Audio Cassette. 2.5 X 4 (Center for Afroamerican and African Studies. Jamaican Study Abroad); CAAS AV AC SA JAM 27.) (Box 29)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-103-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-103-2]
    - Elsa Leo-Rhynie: Status of Women in Jamaica, 1991 June 24; audiocassette; (Status of Women in Jamaica. (1.5 of 1.5) Leo-Rhynie, Elsa. Ann Arbor, Michigan. June 24, 1991. 1.5 Audio Cassette. 2.5 X 4 (Center for Afroamerican and African Studies. Jamaican Study Abroad); CAAS AV AC SA JAM 28) (Box 29)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-104-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-104-2]
    - Baston Lee: A Visit with Baston Lee, 1991 June 27; audiocassette; (Status of Women in Jamaica. Leo-Rhynie, Elsa. Ann Arbor, Michigan. June 27, 1991. 1 Audio Cassette. 2.5 X 4 (Center for Afroamerican and African Studies. Jamaican Study Abroad); CAAS AV AC SA JAM 29.) (Box 29)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-105-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-105-2]
    - Study Abroad in Jamaica Orientation #1, 1991 May 13; audiocassette; (Tape 1; CAAS AV AC SA JAM OR-1. Discussing concerns and logistics of the Jamaica Study Abroad Program.) (Box 29)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-106-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-106-2]
    - Study Abroad in Jamaica Orientation #2, 1991 May 14; audiocassette; (Tape 2; CAAS AV AC SA JAM OR-2. Discussing concerns and logistics of the Jamaica Study Abroad Program.) (Box 29)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-107-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-107-2]
    - Study Abroad in Jamaica Orientation #3, 1991 May 15; audiocassette; (Tape 3; CAAS AV AC SA JAM OR-3. Discussing concerns and logistics of the Jamaica Study Abroad Program.) (Box 29)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-108-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-108-2]
    - Study Abroad in Jamaica Orientation #4, 1991 May 16; audiocassette; (Tape 4; CAAS AV AC SA JAM OR-4) (Box 29)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-109-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-109-2]
  - Gender and Urban Poverty Conference
    - Panel 1, 1996 May 17; audiocassette; (Tape 1; Panel 1 1st 1/2 hour only. Dr. Rose Brewer introducing the panel discussion.) (Box 29)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-110-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-110-2]
    - Panel 2, 1996 May 17; audiocassette; (Tape 1; Panel 2. Unidentified speaker on gender and urban poverty.) (Box 29)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-111-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-111-2]
    - Panel 2, 1996 May 17; audiocassette; (Tape 2; Panel 2; Unidentified speaker on gender and urban poverty.) (Box 29)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-112-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-112-2]
    - Panel 3, 1996 May 17; audiocassette; (Tape 1; Panel 3; Dr. Ronald Hall speaking on skin color and perceptions of it.) (Box 29)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-113-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-113-2]
    - Panel 3, 1996 May 17; audiocassette; (Tape 2; Panel 3; Dr. Ronald Hall speaking on skin color and perceptions of it.) (Box 29)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-114-1]
    - Panel 4, 1996 May 17; audiocassette; (Tape 1; Panel 4; Dr. Ronald Hall speaking on skin color and perceptions of it.) (Box 29)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-115-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-115-2]
    - Panel 4, 1996 May 17; audiocassette; (Tape 2; Panel 4; Dr. Ronald Hall speaking on skin color and perceptions of it.) (Box 29)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-116-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-116-2]
  - Brown Bag
    - Nesha Z. Haniff: Successful Caribbean Women: We had the courage and the vision, 1986 December 04; audiocassette; (12:15-1:20 pm, CAAS Seminar Room; West Engineering Building. U of MichiganCo-sponsored by Center for Continuing Education of Women, Women's Studies Program and Latino Studies; Nesha Z. Haniff, Ph. D.; "Successful Caribbean Women: We Had the Courage and the Vision."; Introduction - Prof. Walter R. Allen) (Box 30)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-117-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-117-2]
    - Adelbert Jenkins: Sustaining self-esteem, 1987 March 26; audiocassette; (Lecture by Adelbert Jenkins entitled "Sustaining Self-Esteem.") (Box 30)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-118-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-118-2]
    - Nesha Haniff: Blaze of Fire: The significant contributions of Caribbean women (A redefinition of success), 1989 February 15; audiocassette; (Talk by Nesha Haniff entitled: "Blaze of Fire: The significant contributions of Caribbean women (A redefinition of success)"; 236 West Engineering.) (Box 30)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-119-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-119-2]
    - Carlene J. Edie: The Seaga to Manley: The impact of the dependency crisis on the 1989 Jamaican Elections, 1989 March 29; audiocassette; (Dr. Carlene J. Edie: Dubois - Mandela - Rodney Post - Doctoral Fellow. Talk entitled "The Seaga to Manley: The impact of the dependency crisis on the 1989 Jamaican Elections." C.A.A.S. Lounge.) (Box 30)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-120-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-120-2]
    - James Jackson: Cross-national perspectives on racism, 1990 October 02; audiocassette; (James Jackson; Associate Dean, Rackham School of Graduate Studies Professor of Psychology "Cross-National Perspectives on Racism" Tuesday, October 2, 1990 Noon; Robert E. Hayden Lounge; 111 West Engineering Bldg.) (Box 30)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-121-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-121-2]
    - Ruth Massinga: Community action for urban and minority students in 1990, 1990 October 30; audiocassette; (Ruth Massinga; Chief Executive, The Casey Foundation and President, American Public Welfare Assocation "Community Action for Urban and Minority Students in 1990"; Tuesday, October 10, 1990 Noon; Robert E. Hayden Lounge; 111 West Engineering Bldg.) (Box 30)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-122-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-122-2]
    - Harold Cruse: Plural but equal: A critical study of blacks and minorities in America's plural society: Implications for ethnic pluralism in the United States, 1990 November 04; audiocassette; (Harold W. Cruse, Professor Emeritus, American Culture and CAAS; "Plural but Equal: A Critical Study of Blacks and Minorities in America's Plural Society: Implications for Ethnic Pluralism in the U.S." Tuesday, November 06, 1990 NoonRobert E. Hayden Lounge, 111 West Engineering Bldg.) (Box 30)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-123-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-123-2]
    - Michael Dawson: Models of black voting behavior, 1990 November 04; audiocassette; (Michael Dawson, Associate Professor of Political Science, "Models of Black Voting Behavior"; Harold W. Cruse; Professor Emeritus, American Culture and CAAS, "Plural but Equal: A Critical Study of Blacks and Minorities in America's Plural Society: Implications for Ethnic Pluralism in the U.S.", Thursday, November 08, 1990 Noon, Robert E. Hayden Lounge, 111 West Engineering Bldg.) (Box 30)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-124-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-124-2]
    - Keletso Atkins: Questionable haven: 19th century emigration schemes for black American settlement in South Africa, 1990 November 13; audiocassette; (Keletso Atkins, Assistant Professor, History and CAAS, "Questionable Haven: 19th Century Emigration Schemes for Black American Settlement in South Africa" Tuesday November 13, 1990 Noon, Robert E. Hayden Lounge, 111 West Engineering Bldg.) (Box 30)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-125-1]
    - Peter Kareithi: The erosion of democracy in Kenya, 1990 November 16; audiocassette; (Peter Kareithi, former Publisher-Editor Financial Review, Nairobi, Kenya. "The Erosion of Democracy: Kenya"; Friday, November 18, 1990 Noon; Robert E. Hayden Lounge, 111 West Engineering Bldg.) (Box 30)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-126-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-126-2]
    - Barry Kistnasamy: Health in transition: Towards a post-apartheid South Africa, 1990 November 20; audiocassette; (Dr. Barry Kistnasamy, Member, African National Congress, Executive Member, National Medical and Dental Assocation of South Africa "Health in Transition: Towards a Post-Aparthied South Africa"; Tuesday November 20, 1990, NoonRobert E. Hayden Lounge, 111 West Engineering Bldg.) (Box 30)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-127-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-127-2]
    - Maria Grosz-Ngate: Reflections on class formation in contemporary Mali, 1990 November 27; audiocassette; (Maria Grosz-Ngate; Visiting Assistant Professor, Anthropology and CAAS "Reflections on Class Formation in Contemporary Mali", Tuesday November 27, 1990 Noon, Robert E. Hayden Lounge, 111 West Engineering Bldg.) (Box 30)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-128-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-128-2]
    - Nesha Haniff: Trying to define indigenous feminist movement among women of color, 1990 December 04; audiocassette; (Nesha Naniff, Assistant Professor, CAAS and Women Studies, "Trying to Define Indigenous Feminist Movement Among Women of Color", Tuesday, December 4, 1990, Noon; Robert E. Hayden Lounge, 111 West Engineering Bldg.) (Box 30)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-129-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-129-2]
    - Neil Foley: The New South in the Southwest: Anglos, Blacks and Chicanos in Central Texas 1880-1930, 1990 December 11; audiocassette; (Neil Foley; King, Chavez, Parks Postdoctoral Fellow; "The New South in the Southwest: Anglos, Blacks and Chicanos in Central Texas 1880-1930"; Tuesday, December 11, 1990, Noon; Robert E. Hayden Lounge111 West Engineering Bldg) (Box 30)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-130-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-130-2]
    - Donald R. Deskins, Jr.: Prospects for minority doctorates in the year 2000: Employment opportunities in a changing America, 1991 January 15; audiocassette; (Donald R. Deskins, Jr. Professor of Sociology; "Prospects for Minority Doctorates in the Year 2000: Employment Opportunities in a Changing America.") (Box 30)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-131-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-131-2]
    - Oscar A. Barbarin: Health and poverty in African-American families: Coping with Sickle Cell Disease, 1991 January 22; audiocassette; (Oscar A. Barbarin, Associate Professor of Social Work. "Health and Poverty in African-American Families: Coping with Sickle Cell Disease" Tuesday, January 22, 1991 12 noon, Robert E. Hayden Lounge. 111 West Engineering Bldg.) (Box 30)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-132-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-132-2]
    - Robert Chrisman: Richard Wright: How Black Women are Portrayed in his Works, 1991 January 29; audiocassette; (Robert Chrisman, Visiting Professor of English and Afroamerican and African Studies. "Richard Wright: How Black Women are Portrayed in his Works." Tuesday January 29, 1991 12 noon, Robert E. Hayden Lounge; 111 West Engineering Building.) (Box 30)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-133-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-133-2]
    - Donna Cochran and Carol Cummings: Cross-Cultural Analyses Women's Health and Well Being: Research at the Institute of Jamaica, 1991 February 04; audiocassette; (Donna Cochran and Carol Cummings; Ph.D. Candidates in Psychology. Cross-Cultural Analyses Women's Health and Well Being: Research at the Institute of Jamaica. Tuesday, February 5, 1991, 12 noon, Robert E. Hayden Lounge; 111 West Engineering Building.) (Box 30)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-134-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-134-2]
    - William McGinley: Literacy as Voice: Understanding Children's Writing About Their Communities and Their Lives, 1991 February 12; audiocassette; (William McGinley; Assistant Professor of Education. :Literacy as Voice: Understanding Children's Writing About Their Communities and Their Lives" Tuesday, February 12, 1991, 12 noon. Robert E. Hayden Lounge; 111 West Engineering Building.) (Box 30)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-135-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-135-2]
    - Ada Ferrer: Race and Nationalism in Eastern Cuba, 1991 February 19; audiocassette; (Ada Ferrer, Graduate Student in History; Race and Nationalism in Eastern Cuba, 1848-1880; Tuesday, February 19, 1991, 12 noon; Robert E. Hayden Lounge, 111 West Engineering Building.) (Box 30)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-136-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-136-2]
    - Huma Ibrahim: Bessie Head: 'Third World' Writer in Exile, 1991 March 04; audiocassette; (Huma Ibrahim; Dubois-Mandela-Rodney Postdoctoral Fellow and Assistant Professor of Literature American University; Bessie Head: "Third World" Writer in Exile; Tuesday March 5, 1991, 12 noon. Robert E. Hayden Lounge; 111 West Engineering Building.) (Box 30)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-137-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-137-2]
    - Teshome G. Wagaw: The Continued Dilemma of Ethnocentrism in Education: African-American Dimensions, 1991 March 12; audiocassette; (Teshome G. Wagaw; Professor of Education and Afroamerican and African Studies; The Continued Dilemma of Ethnocentrism in Education: African-American Dimensions; Tuesday, March 12, 1991, 12 noon. Robert E. Hayden Lounge; 111 West Engineering Building.) (Box 30)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-138-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-138-2]
    - David Labiosa: Strategies of Resistance and Affirmation in 20th Century Caribbean Narrative, 1991 March 19; audiocassette; (David Labiosa; Ph.D. Candidate in Comparative Literature; Strategies of Resistance and Affirmation in 20th Century Caribbean Narrative.; Tuesday, March 19, 1991, 12 noon; Robert E. Hayden Lounge; 111 West Engineering Building.) (Box 30)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-139-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-139-2]
    - Todd Shaw: The Making of Black Mayors: The Black Voter's Criteria for Supporting Black Mayoral Candidacies, 1991 March 26; audiocassette; (David Labiosa; Ph.D. Candidate in Comparative Literature; Strategies of Resistance and Affirmation in 20th Century Caribbean Narrative.; Tuesday, March 19, 1991, 12 noon; Robert E. Hayden Lounge; 111 West Engineering Building.) (Box 30)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-140-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-140-2]
    - Andrew Williams: The Evolution of Ethnicity Among the African Americans of the Dominican Republic, 1991 April 02; audiocassette; (Andrew Williams; Graduate Student in Anthropology; "The Evolution of Ethnicity Among the African Americans of the Dominican Republic"; Tuesday April 2, 199112 noon; Robert E. Hayden Lounge. 111 West Engineering Building.) (Box 30)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-141-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-141-2]
    - N. Frank Ukadike: Colonialism, Christian Missionaries, and African Cinema, 1991 April 04; audiocassette; (N. Frank Ukadike; Lecturer in the Program in Film and Video Studies and Afroamerican and African Studies; Colonialism, Christian Missionaries, and African Cinema"; Tuesday April 9 1991, 12 noon; Robert E. Hayden Lounge111 West Engineering Building.) (Box 30)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-142-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-142-2]
    - Robert Chrisman, Murray Jackson and Melba Boyd: Poetry reading, 1991 June 11; audiocassette; (June 11, 12-1pm; Robert Chrisman Editor and Publisher "The Black Scholar" and Lecturer, CAAS and Department of English, UM; June 18 Murray JacksonAuthor of "Watermelon Rinds and Cherry Pits" and Associate Professor of Education, UM; June 25 Melba Boyd. Author of "Cat Eyes and Dead Wood" and Associate Professor of African-American Studies, UM-Flint.) (Box 30)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-143-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-143-2]
    - Melba Boyd and Lemuel Johnson: Poetry reading, 1991 June 25; audiocassette; (July 2; 12-1pm Lemuel A. Johnson; Author of "Highlife Caliban" and "Hand on the Navel" and Professor of English, UM.; July 9 Myronn Hardy; Author of poems appearing in "Best Poets of 1988" and the "American Poetry Anthology" and CAAS student, UM; July 16 Elise Byrant; Artistic Director, Common Ground Theatre, and Program Assosicate, Labor Studies Center, UM.) (Box 30)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-144-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-144-2]
    - Myron Hardy: Poetry Reading, 1991 July 04; audiocassette; (July 2; 12-1pm Lemuel A. Johnson; Author of "Highlife Caliban" and "Hand on the Navel" and Professor of English, UM.; July 9 Myronn Hardy; Author of poems appearing in "Best Poets of 1988" and the "American Poetry Anthology" and CAAS student, UM; July 16 Elise Byrant; Artistic Director, Common Ground Theatre, and Program Assosicate, Labor Studies Center, UM.) (Box 30)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-145-1]
    - Elise Bryant: Poetry reading, 1991 July 16; audiocassette; (July 2; 12-1pm Lemuel A. Johnson; Author of "Highlife Caliban" and "Hand on the Navel" and Professor of English, UM.; July 9 Myronn Hardy; Author of poems appearing in "Best Poets of 1988" and the "American Poetry Anthology" and CAAS student, UM; July 16 Elise Byrant; Artistic Director, Common Ground Theatre, and Program Assosicate, Labor Studies Center, UM.) (Box 30)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-146-1]
    - Teshome G. Wagaw: The Horn of Africa in Turmoil: The Challenge of Confederation, 1991 September 17; audiocassette; (Professor Teshome G. Wagaw; Professor of Education and Afroamerican and African Studies; "The Horn of Africa in Turmoil: The Challenge of Confederation"; Tuesday, September 17, 1991; 12 Noon - 1:30pm; Robert E. Hayden Lounge111 West Engineering Building.) (Box 30)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-147-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-147-2]
    - Earl Lewis: Reflections on South Africa, 1991 September 24; audiocassette; (Earl Lewis; Director: Center for Afroamerican & African Studies; University of Michigan.) (Box 30)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-148-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-148-2]
    - Sharon P. Holland: Approaches to the Cross-Cultural Study of Native American and African-American Fiction, 1991 October 01; audiocassette; (Sharon P. Holland; Ph.D. Candidate; English Language & Literature; Tuesday October 1, 1991. Robert E. Hayden Lounge. 111 West Engineering Building"Approaches to the Cross-Cultural Study of Native American and African-American Fiction") (Box 30)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-149-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-149-2]
    - Daria C. Kirby: Affirmative Action Programs: An Institutional Analysis, 1991 October 04; audiocassette; (Daria C. Kirby; Ph. D. Candidate in Psychology; Affirmative Action Programs: An Institutional Analysis. Tuesday, October 8, 1991 Robert E. Hayden Lounge111 West Engineering Building.) (Box 30)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-150-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-150-2]
    - Christopher McAuley: The Trinidadian World System: The Work of Cox, James, and Padmore, 1991 October 15; audiocassette; (Christopher McAuley; Graduate Student in Political Science. The Trinidadian World System: The Work of Cox, James, and Padmore. Tuesday, October 15, 1991; Robert E. Hayden Lounge. 111 West Engineering Building.) (Box 30)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-151-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-151-2]
    - Andrea G. Hunter: Constructing Gender: An Exploration of Afro-American Men's Conceptualization of Manhood, 1991 October 22; audiocassette; (Recording unintelligible. Program recorded at very low level and contains loud background noise.] Andrea G. Hunter; King-Chavez-Parks Visiting Professor of Psychology.: "Constructing Gender: An Exploration of Afro-American Men's Conceptualization of Manhood"; Tuesday, October 22, 1991. Robert E. Hayden Lounge. 111 West Engineering Building.) (Box 30)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-152-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-152-2]
    - Director: The CAAS Study Abroad in Jamaica Program: For Prospective Students, A Discussion with the Director and Former Participants in the Spring Term Program in Kingston, 1991 October 29; audiocassette; (Recording unintelligible. Program recorded at very low level and contains loud background noise.] The CAAS Study Abroad in Jamaica Program; For Prospective Students, A Discussion with the Director and Former Participants in the Spring Term Program in Kingston. Tuesday, October 29, 1991. Robert E. Hayden Lounge; 111 West Engineering Building.) (Box 30)